A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller 3rd papers FA108
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Family and Associates Files, 1942-1977 1962-1977; 2; 17.5 Cubic Feet 51 Boxes
  - Works of Art (R), 1962-1971 (Box 48, Folder 409)
  - Works of Art (S), 1962-1971 (Box 48, Folder 410)
  - Works of Art (T-V), 1962-1971 (Box 48, Folder 411)
  - Works of Art (W-Y), 1962-1971 (Box 48, Folder 412)
  - Works of Art (A-C), 1972-1975 (Box 48, Folder 413)
  - Works of Art (D-P), 1972-1975 (Box 48, Folder 414)
  - Works of Art (R-Z), 1972-1975 (Box 48, Folder 415)
  - Works of Art - American Art, 1970-1973 (Box 49, Folder 416)
  - Works of Art - Asia House Gallery Exhibition, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 417)
  - Works of Art - Bluett and Sons, 1959-1965 (Box 49, Folder 418)
    - Bluett and Sons (Box P 171, Folder 24)
  - Works of Art - Boney, Alice, 1961-1965 (Box 49, Folder 419)
    - Boney, Alice (Box P 171, Folder 25)
  - Works of Art - Catalogue Acknowledgements, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 420)
  - Works of Art - Christie, Manson and Woods, Ltd., 1968 (Box 49, Folder 421)
  - Works of Art - Contacts (Europe and Asia), 1959-1965 (Box 49, Folder 422)
  - Works of Art - C.T. Loo and Cie, 1961-1963 (Box 49, Folder 423)
    - C.T. Loo and Cie (Box P 171, Folder 26)
  - Works of Art - John Sparks Ltd., 1961-1969 (Box 49, Folder 424)
  - Works of Art - John Sparks Ltd., 1961-1969 (Box 49, Folder 425)
  - Works of Art - John Sparks Ltd., 1961-1969 (Box 49, Folder 426)
  - Works of Art - John Sparks Ltd., 1970-1971 (Box 50, Folder 427)
  - Works of Art - K. J. Hewett Ltd., 1961-1968 (Box 50, Folder 428)
  - Works of Art - Lee, Sherman E., 1963-1972 (Box 50, Folder 429)
  - Works of Art - Lee, Sherman E., 1963-1972 (Box 50, Folder 430)
  - Works of Art - Moreau-Gobard, J. C., 1961-1963 (Box 50, Folder 431)
  - Works of Art - Richardson, E. P., 1965-1971 (Box 50, Folder 432)
  - Works of Art - Rousset, Robert, 1961-1962 (Box 50, Folder 433)
  - Works of Art - Spink and Son, Ltd., 1959-1964 (Box 50, Folder 434)
  - Works of Art - Spink and Son, Ltd., 1959-1964 (Box 50, Folder 435)
  - Works of Art - Spink and Son, Ltd., 1965-1971 (Box 51, Folder 436)
  - Works of Art - Spink and Son, Ltd., 1965-1971 (Box 51, Folder 437)
  - Works of Art - Spink and Son, Ltd., 1965-1971 (Box 51, Folder 438)
- Office and Homes Files, 1928-1978 1955-1978; 3; 40 Cubic Feet 115 Boxes
  Arranged into nine subseries:
  Subseries 1 - Personal PapersSubseries 2 - CorrespondenceSubseries 3 - Philanthropy and Public InterestsSubseries 4 - Population InterestsSubseries 5 - Asian InterestsSubseries 6 - SpeechesSubseries 7 - TripsSubseries 8 - Subject FileSubseries 9 - Financial Material
  - Personal Papers, 1956-1978; 1
    This subseries contains information on Rockefeller's later years. Of note is the continuation (1962-1978) of the diaries begun in series 1, subseries 1. Also included here are appointment books from 1956 to 1978, which list meeting schedules and participants, along with an occasional reference to the subject to be discusses, as well as telephone logs from 1954 to 1969, which list details of phone calls made or received by Rockefeller. Two sets of index cards containing information on acquaintances, American and foreign business leaders and government officials, and countries are also in this subseries (boxes 16-25). Material related to Rockefeller's extensive art collection including correspondence with galleries, museums, and Edgar P. Richardson, his advisor on American paintings, is also part of this subseries (folders 22-54). While these files do contain some information on his Asian art collection, the bulk of the material on Asian art in this series can be found in subseries 5 (folders 514-519). Records pertaining to the death of JDR 3rd are also contained in this subseries. Condolence letters received by his wife, his son, and the various organizations with which he was associated, as well as a memorial service program and booklet, are filed here (folders 58-74).
    - Appointment Books, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Appointment Books, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Appointment Books, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Appointment Books, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Appointment Books, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Appointment Books, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Appointment Books, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Appointment Books, 1959-1962 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Appointment Books, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Appointment Books, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Appointment Books, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Appointment Books, 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Appointment Books, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Appointment Books, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Appointment Books, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Appointment Books, 1967-1970 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Appointment Books, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Appointment Books, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Appointment Books, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Appointment Books, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Appointment Books, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Appointment Books, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Appointment Books, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Appointment Books, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Art Collection - General, 1967-1978 (Box 7, Folder 24A)
    - Art Collection - General, 1967-1978 (Box 7, Folder 24B)
    - Art Collection - American Art - Disposition, 1974-1978 (Box 7, Folder 24C)
    - Art Collection - American Art - Disposition, 1974-1978 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Art Collection - American Art - Press Releases, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Art Collection - Eskenazi Limited, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Art Collection - European Paintings, 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - European paintings (Box P 171, Folder 27)
    - Art Collection - Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco - Exhibit (April 1976), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Fine Arts Museum of San Francisco - Exhibit (Box P 171, Folder 28)
    - Art Collection - Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco - Exhibit (April 1976), 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Art Collection - Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco - Exhibit (April 1976) - News Clippings (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Art Collection - Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco - Loans, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Art Collection - Fine Arts Museums of San Francisco - White, Ian M., 1970-1972 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Art Collection - Gifts to Children (CLOSED FOLDER), 1976-1978 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Art Collection - Hirschl and Adler Galleries, 1972-1978 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Art Collection - John Sparks, Ltd., 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - John Sparks Ltd. (Box P 171, Folder 29)
    - Art Collection - John Sparks, Ltd., 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Art Collection - Kennedy Galleries, Inc., 1965-1967, 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Art Collection - Kinzen Co., Ltd., 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Art Collection - Kochukyo Co., Ltd., 1973-1978 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Art Collection - Lee, Sherman, 1966-1975 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Art Collection - Marks, Peter, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Art Collection - Mayuyama and Co., Ltd., 1973-1976 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Art Collection - Purchases, 1970-1977 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Art Collection - R. H. Ellsworth, Ltd., 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Art Collection - Richardson, Edgar P., 1967-1978 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Art Collection - Sherrier, Julian, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Art Collection - Spink and Son, Ltd., 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - Spink and Son, Ltd. (Box P 171, Folder 30)
    - Art Collection - Spink and Son, Ltd., 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Art Collection - Thomas Agnew and Sons, Ltd., 1974, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Art Collection - Von Schroeder, Ulrich, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 51)
      - Von Schroeder, Ulrich (Box P 171, Folder 31)
    - Art Collection - Whitney Museum of American Art (September 1976 Exhibit), 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Art Collection - Yabumoto, Shogoro, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Art Collection - Yamaoka, Seibei, 1973-1977 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Baptism, Letter Certifying to, 1921, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Bassett Hall, 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Bassett Hall - Visitors, 1961-1977 (Box 9, Folder 57A)
    - Children, Plans for Care of, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 57B)
    - Death - Certificate of Cremation, July 11, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Death - Condolences Received by - Blanchette, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Death - Condolences Received by - John Davison Rockefeller IV, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Death - Condolences Received by - John Davison Rockefeller IV, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Death - Condolences Received by - John Davison Rockefeller IV, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Death - Condolences Received by - John Davison Rockefeller IV, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Death - Condolences Received by - America-Japan Society, Inc., 1978 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Death - Condolences Received by - Asia Society, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Death - Condolences Received by - Japan Society, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Death - Condolences Received by - John Davison Rockefeller 3rd Fund, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Death - Condolences Received by - Population Council, Inc., 1978 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Death - Condolences Received by - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - Death - Condolences Received by - Rockefeller Foundation, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Death - Condolences Received by - Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    - Death - Memorial Service (Riverside Church) - Booklet, July 13, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    - Death - Memorial Service (Riverside Church) - Booklet - Distribution, July 13, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    - Death - Memorial Service (Riverside Church) - Program, July 13, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    - Diaries, 1962-1967 (Box 11, Folder 75)
    - Diaries, 1962-1967 (Box 11, Folder 76)
    - Diaries, 1962-1967 (Box 11, Folder 77)
    - Diaries, 1962-1967 (Box 11, Folder 78)
    - Diaries, 1962-1967 (Box 11, Folder 79)
    - Diaries, 1962-1967 (Box 11, Folder 80)
    - Diaries, 1968-1972 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - Diaries, 1968-1972 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - Diaries, 1968-1972 (Box 12, Folder 83)
    - Diaries, 1968-1972 (Box 12, Folder 84)
    - Diaries, 1968-1972 (Box 12, Folder 85)
    - Diaries, 1973-May 1977 (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - Diaries, 1973-May 1977 (Box 13, Folder 87)
    - Diaries, 1973-May 1977 (Box 13, Folder 88)
    - Diaries, 1973-May 1977 (Box 13, Folder 89)
    - Diaries, 1973-May 1977 (Box 13, Folder 90)
    - Diaries, 1973-May 1977 (Box 13, Folder 91)
    - Diaries, June 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 92)
    - Diaries, June 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 93)
    - Doctors, 1972-1978 (Box 14, Folder 94)
    - Fallout Shelters, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 95)
    - Fieldwood Farm, 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 96)
    - Fieldwood Farm - Construction Specifications, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 97)
    - Fieldwood Farm - Social Lists, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 98)
    - Golf Lessons, 1967-1973, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 99)
    - Greenrock Corporation, 1969-1976 (Box 14, Folder 100)
    - Greenrock Corporation - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 101)
    - Hospitality and Social Lists, 1965, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 102)
    - Honorary Degrees, Listing of, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 103)
    - Millstream Cottage, 1972-1975 (Box 15, Folder 104)
    - One Beekman Place, 1972-1975 (Box 15, Folder 105)
    - One Beekman Place, 1972-1975 (Box 15, Folder 106)
    - Pocantico Hills, 1972-1978 (Box 26, Folder 107)
    - Pocantico Hills, 1972-1978 (Box 26, Folder 108)
      - Quilt (Box P 171, Folder 32)
    - Pocantico Hills, 1972-1978 (Box 26, Folder 109)
    - Pocantico Hills - Goldstone (Harmon) Catalog Project, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 110)
    - Telephone Logs - Books I-VI, June 1954-September 1956 (Box 26, Folder 111)
    - Telephone Logs - Books I-VI, June 1954-September 1956 (Box 26, Folder 112)
    - Telephone Logs - Books I-VI, June 1954-September 1956 (Box 26, Folder 113)
    - Telephone Logs - Books VII-XVIII, September 1956-March 1961 (Box 27, Folder 114)
    - Telephone Logs - Books VII-XVIII, September 1956-March 1961 (Box 27, Folder 115)
    - Telephone Logs - Books VII-XVIII, September 1956-March 1961 (Box 27, Folder 116)
    - Telephone Logs - Books VII-XVIII, September 1956-March 1961 (Box 27, Folder 117)
    - Telephone Logs - Books VII-XVIII, September 1956-March 1961 (Box 27, Folder 118)
    - Telephone Logs - Books VII-XVIII, September 1956-March 1961 (Box 27, Folder 119)
    - Telephone Logs - Books XIX-XXX, March 1961-December 1964 (Box 28, Folder 120)
    - Telephone Logs - Books XIX-XXX, March 1961-December 1964 (Box 28, Folder 121)
    - Telephone Logs - Books XIX-XXX, March 1961-December 1964 (Box 28, Folder 122)
    - Telephone Logs - Books XIX-XXX, March 1961-December 1964 (Box 28, Folder 123)
    - Telephone Logs - Books XIX-XXX, March 1961-December 1964 (Box 28, Folder 124)
    - Telephone Logs - Books XIX-XXX, March 1961-December 1964 (Box 28, Folder 125)
    - Telephone Logs - Books XXXI-XXXIII, December 1964-April 1966 (Box 29, Folder 126)
    - Telephone Logs - Books XXXI-XXXIII, December 1964-April 1966 (Box 29, Folder 127)
    - Telephone Logs - Unnumbered, April 1966-November 1969 (Box 29, Folder 128)
    - Telephone Logs - Unnumbered, April 1966-November 1969 (Box 29, Folder 129)
    - Mills Stem Cottage: House of Mr. and Mrs. JDR 3rd - North Haven, Maine- existing conditions- 2nd floor plan- #2, 1956 September 11; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 2, Folder 97)
    - Mills Stem Cottage: House of Mr. and Mrs. JDR 3rd - North Haven, Maine- existing conditions- 1st floor plan- #1- Mr. JDR 3rd- North Haven- Mills Stem Cottage, 1956 September 11; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 2, Folder 97)
    - Mills Stem Cottage: Plans showing a portion of the Arthur W. and Anna A. Beverage Form- North Haven, ME-conveyed to JDR 3rd- GF 293 North Haven (Edward W. Coffin, Surveyor), 1967 August; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer B 2, Folder 97)
    - Mills Stem Cottage: Plans showing land of Thomas W. Lamont at Pulpit Harbor, North Haven, ME- Rockland, ME #3- Plans showing Thomas W. Lamont, North Haven, ME. Mr. JDR 3rd- Mill Strawn Cottage (Office of O.H. Tripp Engineering Co), 1938 February; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Drawer B 2, Folder 97)
    - Mills Stem Cottage: Plans showing land of Thomas W. Lamont at Pulpit Harbor, North Haven, ME- #3A (scale not accurate on this photostat, reduced in size for blueprint), 1938 February (Drawer B 2, Folder 97)
    - Rockefeller cemetery map and fallout shelters plans, Quantity: 3 (Box Cabinet B Drawer 2, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence, 1935-1978 1962-1978; 2
    Arranged into personal, chronological, and alphabetical sections.
    This correspondence documents Rockefeller's business, civic, governmental, philanthropic, cultural, and social activities. The personal correspondence contains incoming and outgoing letters from family members, friends, associates, and American and foreign government officials. The "Famous People" correspondents (folders 137-138) include Rosalyn Carter, Kurt Waldheim, and members of Congress and the presidential cabinets. Letters between Rockefeller and Charles Percy, John D. Rockefeller IV's father-in-law, reveal the warm relationship between the two families. Also located in this subseries are letters from Shigeharu Matsumoto and his family, close personal friends with whom the Rockefellers visited during their numerous trips to Japan. This section also contains correspondence between Rockefeller and his associates David K. Lelewer, Donald H. McLean, Jr., and Datus C. Smith, Jr. The chronological file contains copies of Rockefeller's outgoing correspondence from 1970 to 1978. The alphabetical file contains outgoing correspondence for the year 1978 filed by name of the recipient.
    - Personal, 1962-1964 (Box 30, Folder 130)
    - Personal, 1962-1964 (Box 30, Folder 131)
    - Personal, 1972-1975 (Box 30, Folder 132)
    - Personal - Aldrich, Winthrop, 1961, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 133)
    - Personal - Case, Laura, 1958-1968 (Box 30, Folder 134)
    - Personal - Family, 1966-1978 (Box 30, Folder 135)
    - Personal - Family, 1966-1978 (Box 30, Folder 136)
    - Personal - "Famous People", 1966-1977 (Box 30, Folder 137)
    - Personal - "Famous People", 1966-1977 (Box 30, Folder 138)
    - Personal - Harr, John E., 1969-1978 (Box 30, Folder 139)
    - Personal - Hooker, Barbara, 1935, 1960-1978 (Box 30, Folder 140)
    - Personal - Kosygin, Aleksei N., 1967-1968 (Box 30, Folder 141)
    - Personal - Lelewer, David K., 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 142)
    - Personal - McCracken, Robert J., 1958-1967 (Box 31, Folder 143)
    - Personal - McLean, Donald H., Jr., 1951-1965 (Box 31, Folder 144)
    - Personal - McNulty, John, 1966-1968 (Box 31, Folder 145)
    - Personal - Marquand Family, 1939-1970 (Box 31, Folder 146)
    - Personal - Matsumoto Family, 1959-1977 (Box 31, Folder 147)
    - Personal - Mauze, Abby Rockefeller, 1955-1976 (Box 31, Folder 148)
    - Personal - O'Malley Family, 1950-1975 (Box 31, Folder 149)
    - Personal - Percy, Charles, 1967-1978 (Box 31, Folder 150)
    - Personal - Pierson, Ann Rockefeller, 1960, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 151)
    - Personal - Rockefeller, Martha Baird, 1961-1968 (Box 31, Folder 152)
    - Personal - Rockefeller, Winthrop, 1962-1973 (Box 31, Folder 154)
    - Personal - Roelofs, Helen and Robert, 1957-1969 (Box 31, Folder 155)
    - Personal - Rosendahl, William J., 1971 (Box 31, Folder 156)
    - Personal - Rusk, Dean, 1960-1966 (Box 31, Folder 157)
    - Personal - Smith, Datus C., Jr., 1964-1972 (Box 31, Folder 158)
    - Personal - Sweetser Family, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 159)
    - Personal - Young, Kenneth T., Jr., 1958-1972 (Box 31, Folder 160)
    - Chronological File, January 1970-December 1970 (Box 32, Folder 161)
    - Chronological File, January 1970-December 1970 (Box 32, Folder 162)
    - Chronological File, January 1970-December 1970 (Box 32, Folder 163)
    - Chronological File, January 1970-December 1970 (Box 32, Folder 164)
    - Chronological File, January 1970-December 1970 (Box 32, Folder 165)
    - Chronological File, January 1970-December 1970 (Box 32, Folder 166)
    - Chronological File, January 1970-December 1970 (Box 32, Folder 167)
    - Chronological File, January 1970-December 1970 (Box 32, Folder 168)
    - Chronological File, January 1970-December 1970 (Box 32, Folder 169)
    - Chronological File, January 1970-December 1970 (Box 32, Folder 170)
    - Chronological File, Januar 1971-September 1971 (Box 33, Folder 171)
    - Chronological File, Januar 1971-September 1971 (Box 33, Folder 172)
    - Chronological File, Januar 1971-September 1971 (Box 33, Folder 173)
    - Chronological File, Januar 1971-September 1971 (Box 33, Folder 174)
    - Chronological File, Januar 1971-September 1971 (Box 33, Folder 175)
    - Chronological File, Januar 1971-September 1971 (Box 33, Folder 176)
    - Chronological File, Januar 1971-September 1971 (Box 33, Folder 177)
    - Chronological File, Januar 1971-September 1971 (Box 33, Folder 178)
    - Chronological File, October 1971-October 1972 (Box 34, Folder 179)
    - Chronological File, October 1971-October 1972 (Box 34, Folder 180)
    - Chronological File, October 1971-October 1972 (Box 34, Folder 181)
    - Chronological File, October 1971-October 1972 (Box 34, Folder 182)
    - Chronological File, October 1971-October 1972 (Box 34, Folder 183)
    - Chronological File, October 1971-October 1972 (Box 34, Folder 184)
    - Chronological File, October 1971-October 1972 (Box 34, Folder 185)
    - Chronological File, October 1971-October 1972 (Box 34, Folder 186)
    - Chronological File, October 1971-October 1972 (Box 34, Folder 187)
    - Chronological File, October 1971-October 1972 (Box 34, Folder 188)
    - Chronological File, October 1971-October 1972 (Box 34, Folder 189)
    - Chronological File, October 1971-October 1972 (Box 34, Folder 190)
    - Chronological File, November 1972-June 1973 (Box 35, Folder 191)
    - Chronological File, November 1972-June 1973 (Box 35, Folder 192)
    - Chronological File, November 1972-June 1973 (Box 35, Folder 193)
    - Chronological File, November 1972-June 1973 (Box 35, Folder 194)
    - Chronological File, November 1972-June 1973 (Box 35, Folder 195)
    - Chronological File, November 1972-June 1973 (Box 35, Folder 196)
    - Chronological File, July 1973-December 1973 (Box 36, Folder 197)
    - Chronological File, July 1973-December 1973 (Box 36, Folder 198)
    - Chronological File, July 1973-December 1973 (Box 36, Folder 199)
    - Chronological File, July 1973-December 1973 (Box 36, Folder 200)
    - Chronological File - Index, 1974-1976 (Box 36, Folder 201)
    - Chronological File, January 1974-April 1974 (Box 36, Folder 202)
    - Chronological File, January 1974-April 1974 (Box 36, Folder 203)
    - Chronological File, January 1974-April 1974 (Box 36, Folder 204)
    - Chronological File, May 1974-June 1975 (Box 37, Folder 205)
    - Chronological File, May 1974-June 1975 (Box 37, Folder 206)
    - Chronological File, May 1974-June 1975 (Box 37, Folder 207)
    - Chronological File, May 1974-June 1975 (Box 37, Folder 208)
    - Chronological File, May 1974-June 1975 (Box 37, Folder 209)
    - Chronological File, May 1974-June 1975 (Box 37, Folder 210)
    - Chronological File, May 1974-June 1975 (Box 37, Folder 211)
    - Chronological File, July 1975-July 1976 (Box 38, Folder 212)
    - Chronological File, July 1975-July 1976 (Box 38, Folder 213)
    - Chronological File, July 1975-July 1976 (Box 38, Folder 214)
    - Chronological File, July 1975-July 1976 (Box 38, Folder 215)
    - Chronological File, July 1975-July 1976 (Box 38, Folder 216)
    - Chronological File, July 1975-July 1976 (Box 38, Folder 217)
    - Chronological File, July 1975-July 1976 (Box 38, Folder 218)
    - Chronological File, August 1976-December 1976 (Box 39, Folder 219)
    - Chronological File, August 1976-December 1976 (Box 39, Folder 220)
    - Chronological File - Index, 1977 (Box 39, Folder 221)
    - Chronological File, January 1977-August 1977 (Box 39, Folder 222)
    - Chronological File, January 1977-August 1977 (Box 39, Folder 223)
    - Chronological File, January 1977-August 1977 (Box 39, Folder 224)
    - Chronological File, January 1977-August 1977 (Box 39, Folder 225)
    - Chronological File, September 1977-December 1977 (Box 40, Folder 226)
    - Chronological File, September 1977-December 1977 (Box 40, Folder 227)
    - Chronological File - Index, 1978 (Box 40, Folder 228)
    - Chronological File, January 1978-July 1978 (Box 40, Folder 229)
    - Chronological File, January 1978-July 1978 (Box 40, Folder 230)
    - Chronological File, January 1978-July 1978 (Box 40, Folder 231)
    - Alphabetical (A-C), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 232)
    - Alphabetical (D-G), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 233)
    - Alphabetical (H-L), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 234)
    - Alphabetical (M-P), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 235)
    - Alphabetical (R-S), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 236)
    - Alphabetical (T-Z), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 237)
  - Philanthropy and Public Interests, 1937-1978 1952-1978; 3
    Arranged alphabetically by subject or name of organization.